https://labelsusa.com/privacy-policy/

675 Florida Central Pkwy, Longwood, Florida 32750, USA407-830-9500M-F | 9:00 AM - 6:00 PM FacebookTwitterLinkedinFoursquare
Home Products Information FTP Video Testimonials ContactQuick Quote
Privacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy Policy
LabelsUSA.com
Your Privacy
Labels USA, Inc. respects your privacy. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Labels USA, Inc.
Credit Card Details
Your credit card information is secured by SSL, a C.O.M.O.D.O. site.
External Sites
Labels USA, Inc. is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Labels USA, Inc. to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Labels USA, Inc. does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.
Internet Risks
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Labels USA, Inc., except credit card information. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Labels USA, Inc. have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Questions & Concerns
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies. For any other information email info@labelsusa.com
